# CURICULUM VITAE







# MUHAMMAD SHOAIB

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER



shoaibbabar098@gmail.com



0315 - 1080450



E#1182 Orangi Town, Karachi

# **ABOUT ME**

I am Frontend developer having expertise in JavaScript, React.js, Next.js, Ui/Ux and other mentioned skills. I create responsive and user-friendly web applications. I am doing Bachelors in Software Engineering from Sindh Madressatul Islam University (SMIU).

#### **OBJECTIVE**

To become an expert for the progress of an organization by utilizing my skills & knowledge of the field in a challenging environment.

# **EDUCATION**

**B.S Software Engineering** | Sep 2020 - Present Sindh Madressatul Islam University

INTERMEDIATE | Sep 2017 - June 2019 Sindh Muslim Gevernment Science College

MATRICULATION | April 2015 - May 2017 Karachi Secondary Board

# **SKILLS**

HTML React.js Photoshop

CSS Next.js Illustrator

JavaScript WordPress

Bootstrap Php

Tailwind CSS Ui/Ux (Figma)

# **CERTIFICATE**

WEB & APP DEVELOPMENT | Dec 2022 - Dec 2023

Saylani Mass IT Training

CLOUD COMPUTING June 2022 - Dec 2023

Piaic

GRAPHIC DESIGNING | May 2021 - Aug 2021

Click 5

# **EXPERIENCE**

Frontend Developer Intern March 2024 - Present

at OneClick Digital

Faculty Member July 2023 - Jan 2024

at Aptech Learning

# **PORTFOLIO**

https://muhammad-shoaib.vercel.app